

GHANA

Pharmacy Council

THE HEALTH PROFESSIONS REGULATORY BODIES ACT, 2013 (ACT 857) PART FOUR, SECTION 82

Certificate of Registration As A Pharmacy Technician

This is to certify that

KUYIBA ANTHONY

Date of Registration _28TH MARCH, 2023 PIN No. _

PT2630/2023

REGISTRAR, PHARMACY COUNCI

CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: Kuyiba Anthony

Gender: Male

Date of Birth: 16th October, 1993

Nationality: Ghanaian

Marital Status: Single

Language(s) spoken: Asante Twi, Gruci and English

Residential Address: Bechem Presec Box 81

Hometown: Navrongo – Upper East Region

Personal Contact: 0548174628

Emergency Contact: +233548174628.

E-Mail: akuyiba8@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

Highly trained pharmacy technician with two years hospital pharmacy experience and with strong clinical abilities and a successful career in both hospital and insurance facilities. Proactive and organized with passionate commitment to first-rate patient care.

SKILLS:

- Manual and automated medication dispensing.
- Active listening skills and advance math skills.
- Drug storage procedures.
- Pharmacy and customer record management.
- Reconstitution and admixture preparations.
- Organizational and multitasking abilities,
- Drug inventory management.
- Websites and mobile apps development ----- In progress.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

- 1. Pharmacy Technician, 10/2022 to date.
 - Afua Kobi Hospital, Adugyama-Adum Kumasi.
- 2. National Service Personnel, 08/2021 To 09/2022.

Bechem Government Hospital, Bechem-Ahafo Region.

Work:

- a. Medication dispensing.
- b. Assisted patient in minimizing medical expenses by recommending generic medical prescription medications.
- c. Verify patient data and billing information to discover and resolve erroneous bills due to system errors.
- d. Stocked, labeled and inventoried medications to keep accurate records.
- e. Medication pre-packing.
- f. Handling and evaluation of prescription.
- g. Assisting pharmacist in medication inventory and distribution.
- 3. Pharmacy Interns, 06/2019 To 08/2019 and 07/2020 To 09/2020. Bechem Government Hospital, Bechem-Ahafo Region.

Work:

- a. Pre-packing of medications.
- b. Extemporaneous preparations.
- c. Dispensing of medications to patient.
- d. Compare prescription details against safety standards and insurance requirements to support patients.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Tertiary	
Institution:	Sunyani Technical University 2018-2021
Qualification:	Higher National Diploma (HND)
Course:	HND Pharmacy Technician
Location:	Sunyani
Senior High School	•
Institution:	Presbyterian Senior high school 2013-2016
Qualification:	W.A.S.S.C.E
Location:	Bechem-Ahafo Region

Junior High School	
Institution:	Presbyterian Junior High school 2010 – 2013
Qualification:	B.E.C.E
Position held: Location:	Section Leader Bechem – Ahafo Region
PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES	
Good in academic	Honest
Diligent	Hardworking
HOBBIES	
Reading	Listening to music
Football	Watching movies
REFEREES	
1. Name:	Pharm. Philip Opoku
	(Clinical Pharmacist specialist at Bechem Government Hospital)
Phone Number:	0243261894
2. Name:	Pharm. Patrick Appiah Larbi (Senior Pharmacist at Kenyasi Hospital)

0244788197

(Pharmacy Technician at Bechem Government Hospital)

Rachael Anane

0241035509

Phone Number:

Phone Number:

3. Name:

NATIONAL BOARD FOR PROFESSIONAL AND TECHNICIAN EXAMINATIONS (NABPTEX) GHANA

AND THE RESTANCE OF THE PARTY O





This is to certify that

KUYIBA, ANTHONY

having pursued the prescribed programme of studies

SUNYANI TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

at

and having passed the prescribed examinations

10th September, 2021

by

has been awarded the HIGHER NATIONAL DIPLOMA in

DISPENSING TECHNOLOGY

FIRST CLASS

Certificate No. I 0025496

Candidate No_

06181173



EXECUTIVE SECRETARY, NABPTEX

Dated the ____ day of ___ March, 2022

In case of reply please quote reference number

Our Ref. STU/433/169

Your Ref:...

Date: OCT 12,2022

TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN

TESTIMONIAL

MR. KUYIBA ANTHONY

This is to testify that the above-named person is a past student of this University (formerly Sunyani Polytechnic).

MR. KUYIBA ANTHONY was admitted into this University during the 2018/2019 academic year to pursue the Higher National Diploma (HND) Programme in Dispensing Technology.

He completed his course of study in September 2021 and obtained a First Class.

We would be grateful if you could give him the necessary assistance.

SIL SIL

SIU SIU

TIN STI

Thank you.

J. K MANU

DEPUTY REGISTRAR (ACADEMICS AFFAIRS)

FOR: REGISTRAR

DEPUTY REGISTRAR
ACADEMIC AFFAIRS & ADMISSIONS
SUNYANI TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY
P. O. BOX 206
SUNYANI BIA